Charles R. Martin Photographs, 1945-2011 AIS.2012.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Negatives, 1945-1998; II.
  - 35mm Negatives, 1.
    - 1970
      - United Fund- Red Cross Phone Jobs, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 35-36)
      - Personal- Ocracoke- CPS Color, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 37)
      - Beckman, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 38-39)
      - Pflaum Copies- B&S Associate Slide, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 40)
      - United Fund- Diabetic Girl, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 41-43)
      - United Fund- Red Cross Phone Volunteers, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 44)
      - United Fund- Red Cross Volunteers at VA Hospital, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 45-46)
      - United Fund- Pennsylvania Association for Blind, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 47-48)
      - United Fund- Nurse Rita Kelly Verma, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 50)
      - United Fund- Nurse Rita Kelly Verma, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Pressley Ridge, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 2-6, 15-16, 18-19)
      - United Fund- C.C. Meeting, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 7-9, 33, 37)
      - United Fund- Brashear Center, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 10-11)
      - Personal, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 12, 28, 42-44, 48)
      - Media Graphics- ICM, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - United Fund, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 14, 34-36, 38-41)
      - American Bridge Copies, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - ICM- Canon, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Cross Electronics, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - United Fund- Millvale Volunteers Meeting, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - United Fund- Rita Kelly Verma w/ Patients, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - Goodwill, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 24-26, 29-32)
      - United Fund, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 34-36, 38-41, 45)
      - Vibra-Tech, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 46)
      - Keith Swenson, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 47)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 49)
      - United Fund- Board Meeting, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 50)
      - United Fund- Board Meeting, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 3-9)
    - 1971
      Subjects include the Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children; United Fund; Chatham College; Media Graphics; Easter Seals; Wexford Folk Festival; ICM School of Business. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Chatham College, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 10-11)
      - Personal, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 12-13, 18, 27)
      - Chatham College- Copy Job, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 15-17, 30-43, 45-46, 50)
      - Personal, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 47)
      - H.E.W. Meeting, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 19-20)
      - Goodwill, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 21-26)
      - VT Brick Crack Pix, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - VT Brochure Pix, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - Personal- Deep Creek, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 44)
      - Summarit Test, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 48-49)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 1-3, 5-7, 9-12, 35, 37-39, 43-49)
      - Musical Playing, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Personal, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 8, 13, 16-18, 25-26, 36)
      - Goodwill, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Goodwill- Copy Work, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - United Fund- Irene Kaufman Settlement House, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 19-24)
      - Health – O – Rama, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 27-30)
      - Salvation Army, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 31-33)
      - Personal- Shadyside Area, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - Chatham College, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 40-41)
      - Passports (?), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 42)
      - Wexford Folk Festival, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 50)
      - Wexford Folk Festival, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 4-6, 15, 18-22)
      - United Fund- Meeting, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 7, 11)
      - United Fund, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 8-10)
      - Personal- 9th Grade Party North Hills, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Troop Property, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Personal- Cannon & Summarit, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Personal- Mary Stewart- Canon-Summarit, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Test, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 17, 38)
      - ICM, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 23-26, 31-37)
      - Personal, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - Personal- Capture of Moby Duck, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - Personal- M. 3 Test Summarit, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 29-30)
      - United Fund- Carnegie Boys Club, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 39-42)
      - Personal- Cat, Ducks & Sal, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 43)
      - Lisfeldt- Copy Work, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 44)
      - Easter Seals- Camp Variety, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 45-53)
      - United Fund- Visiting Nurses Association, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 1-3, 5)
      - United Fund- Visiting Nurses Association- McKeesport, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Personal- Camera Test, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 6-7, 17)
      - United Fund- Vols. Munhall, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Personal- Ocracoke, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 9-10)
      - United Fund- Copies of Barry Sullivan, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Symphony Opening Night, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 12-13)
      - VT Brochure Work, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - United Fund - Health -O - Rama, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 15-16)
      - R. K. Mellon Foundation, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 18-25)
      - Gail Fithian (?), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 26-27)
      - Personal, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 28, 36)
      - Larry Zunic- LCB Pix, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - CC Mtg., 1971 (Box 25, Folder 30, 34-35, 39-41, 50-51, 54)
      - Easter Seals- Bob w/ X-mas Poinsettia, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 31)
      - Bucs Win Series- Pittsburgh, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 32)
      - Chargers– Steelers, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 33)
      - Personal- Light Up Night- Pittsburgh, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 37)
      - Personal- Cat, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 38)
      - 13 Mile YMCA Run- North Park to Pittsburgh, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 42)
      - Clarion Area, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 43)
      - Misc. Personal & Clarion, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 44)
      - Summitar Test, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 45)
      - Media Graphics- Office, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 46)
      - United Fund, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 47)
      - United Fund- Workers Party, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 48-49)
      - M3 Summarit, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 52)
      - Summarit, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 53)
      - R. K. Mellon Foundation, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 55)
      - R. K. Mellon Foundation, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
      - Personal, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - KITS Pix, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Chatham College- Foundation Reading Program, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 5-7)
      - Chatham College- Slide Copies, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - United Fund- Meeting, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 9, 27)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- Farm, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 10-17)
      - Lando- H&M, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 18-23)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- Christmas, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 24-26)
      - Camp Fire Girls, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 28, 32)
      - Regan- Copy Work, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 29)
      - KITS- Wrestling, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 30)
      - CC- D. Nimmick, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 31)
      - Mellon- Old P.O., 1971 (Box 26, Folder 33)
      - United Fund- Volunteers, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 34-35)
    - 1972
      Subjects include United Fund; Chatham College; Cross Electronics; Pittsburgh Steelers; Salvation Army; ICM School of Business; R.K. Mellon; Health Research and Service Foundation (HRSF); Halstead & Mitchell; Wexford Folk Festival. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Personal- Dog & Cat, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 36)
      - Personal, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 37)
      - Easter Seals, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 38-44)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 45-47)
      - R. K. Mellon Foundation Job, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 48-49)
      - Beckman (Slide Copies), 1972 (Box 26, Folder 50)
      - Kit, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 51)
      - Health Research and Service Foundation- Mary Forrest, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 52-53)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 1-13, 36-39, 41-42, 51)
      - Lando- Cups, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 14, 16)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children - Boyce, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 15, 17-18)
      - R. K. Mellon Foundation, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 19-22)
      - Halstead & Mitchell- Lando, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 23-27)
      - R.K. Mellon Foundation- Allegheny Community College, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 28-29)
      - F G-7 Test, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 30-34)
      - D-76 Test, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 35)
      - Summarit # Test F6-7, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 40)
      - Summarit # Test, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 43)
      - Colorado, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 44-50)
      - Chatham College, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 52-54)
      - Chatham College, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 1-7, 23-27, 29, 34)
      - CC Show- Kit, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Kit, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Beckman P.P - Pix, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Summarit # Test, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - United Fund- Workshop, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Salvation Army, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 13-17)
      - United Fund- CC Workshop, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 18, 20-22, 39)
      - United Fund - VRC Tour, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 28, 32-33, 42)
      - United Fund- CC, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 30-31, 35-38)
      - Elizabeth Barner, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 40)
      - Beckman Kids, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 41)
      - Wexford Folk Festival, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 43-44, 50-51)
      - United Fund- Cerebral Palsy- Wilkinsburg, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 45)
      - United Fund- Cerebral Palsy- North Hills, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 46-48)
      - Pollution- Pittsburgh, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 49)
      - Mais Graduation, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 52)
      - United Fund- Allocations Meeting, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 1-6)
      - Kathryn Kuhlman, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 7-12)
      - Wexford Folk Festival, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 13-14)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- Commencement, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 15-16)
      - United Fund- CC- Youth City/ South Park, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 17-18)
      - Personal, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - CC Meeting, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 20, 23)
      - United Fund- Meeting, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 21-22)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 24-29, 31-32)
      - United Fund, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 30)
      - United Fund - John T. Mauro - P.A.T., 1972 (Box 29, Folder 33)
      - United Fund - Cerebral Palsy - Pittsburgh, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 34-38)
      - H & W Association, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 39-41)
      - United Fund/CC- C.P.- Baldwin Lela, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 42)
      - United Fund- Cerebral Palsy- North Hills, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 43-44, 49-50)
      - United Fund- Cerebral Palsy- South Hills (Baldwin), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 45)
      - United Fund /CC- Cerebral Palsy- South Hills, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 46-47)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center- Tour, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 48)
      - United Fund- Cerebral Palsy- Wilkinsburg, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 51-52)
      - United Fund- Golden Age Club S.A., 1972 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
      - United Fund- Louise Child Care, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 3-9, 13)
      - United Fund- Girl Scout– Penn Hills, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - United Fund- L (Lemmington?) Home for the Aged, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 11-12, 14)
      - Halstead & Mitchell, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 15-18)
      - United Fund/CC, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 19-20)
      - CC- Mrs. D. Richardson - H & Welfare Association, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - United Fund, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 22-23)
      - United Fund- at Salvation Army, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 24-25)
      - United Fund- (?), 1972 (Box 30, Folder 26)
      - Media Graphics- ICM, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 27-35)
      - United Fund- Youth in Trouble, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 36-37)
      - United Fund- Vocational Rehabilitation Center - Case "Patty", 1972 (Box 30, Folder 38-39)
      - United Fund- Meeting at Mellon Bank, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 40, 45)
      - Mrs. Kelly- M & C. Server, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 41)
      - Judy Bricker- MS Case, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - Carolyn Graham- MS Case, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 43)
      - Muldred Maker- MS Case, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 44)
      - United Fund- Boys Club, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 46-47)
      - United Fund- Boys Club- YIKC Park, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 48)
      - United Fund- YIKC, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - Copy of William Pitt Painting, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 50)
      - United Fund- Family & Child Services, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 51-52)
      - United Fund- Stroke Patients, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
      - United Fund- Cerebral Palsy- Pittsburgh, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 3-5)
      - United Fund- Jewish Home, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 6-8)
      - United Fund- Rippling Water, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - United Fund- Crowds, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 10-11)
      - United Fund- Deaf, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 12-13)
      - C.C. Meeting, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 14-15, 21-22)
      - Chatham College, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 16, 29-30)
      - Personal- Wyoming, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 17-18)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 19-20)
      - United Fund- McKees Rocks- Boys Club, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - United Fund- Captain Wilson- Salvation Army, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 24)
      - United Fund- Major Shafstall- Salvation Army– Braddock, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 25)
      - United Fund- McKees Rocks- Boys Club– David Lee Wayne, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 26)
      - Salvation Army- Captain Williams, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 27)
      - United Fund- Campaign Edition- Kids, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 28)
      - United Fund- Campaign Edition Sign- Louise Child Care Center, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 31-32)
      - Personal- Labor Day, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 33)
      - Personal- Devils Tower- Wyoming, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 34)
      - Personal - Sal & Byron, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 35)
      - United Fund- Paul Jenkins, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 36)
      - Personal- Elmar, Summarit Test, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 37)
      - United Fund- Mrs. Karl Krasik- Squirrel Hill, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 38)
      - C/C- Mr. Halpern, & Mr. Ramsdell, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 39)
      - United Fund, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 40-44)
      - Steelers- (Special), 1972 (Box 31, Folder 45-48)
      - United Fund- Volunteers- Business Solicitors- Mr. Papa (Miller), 1972 (Box 31, Folder 49)
      - United Fund- Deaf Girl- Valerie Quayle, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 50)
      - United Fund- Volunteer Meetings, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 51)
      - KK (?), 1972 (Box 31, Folder 52)
      - KK (?), 1972 (Box 32, Folder 1-3, 6)
      - C. C.- Sewickley Community Center, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 4-5, 10)
      - C.C.- Y.I.K.C., 1972 (Box 32, Folder 7-9)
      - Personal, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - United Fund/ CC- Cerebral Palsy, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 12-14)
      - United Fund- Displays, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Bush's Wedding- Beverly, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - F.I.C.- Dr. Eddy- Chatham College, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 19-23, 28-31)
      - Personal- Dad's 80th Birthday, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Chatham College- H.S. Seminar, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 25-27)
      - Cross Electronics, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - Personal, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 33)
      - Personal- IIIA. Summarit, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 34-35)
      - Halstead & Mitchell, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 36-37)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- Maria & Cake, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 38)
      - Chatham College, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 39)
      - United Fund/ CC, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 40-43)
      - CC- Campfire Girls/Homewood, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 44)
      - Lando- Halstead & Mitchell- Alabama, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 45-47)
      - Memphis Airport, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - 1973
      Subjects include Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children; Community Services of Pennsylvania; Chatham College; United Fund; Vocational Rehabilitation; Health Research & Services Foundation (HRSF); Kellogg Media Group (KMG); unidentified images. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Personal, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 49)
      - Personal- IIIa Summarit, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 50)
      - Lando- H.I. Wynne, Arkansas, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 1-12)
      - Lando- Youngstown, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 13-14)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- at Buhl, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 15-18)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 19-22)
      - Personal No. "40", 1973 (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - United Fund Awards – Editors- Dinner Meeting- Stouffers, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 24)
      - Personal- Mac & Pitt Swim Meet- West Virginia, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - Nationwide District Sales Group, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 26)
      - Health Research & Services Foundation, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 27-31)
      - Personal- Leica II Test, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 32)
      - Personal- Sewickley, North Hills, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 33)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation Center, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 34-48)
      - Personal- Tom, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 49)
      - United Fund- Cerebral Palsy – Bell Telephone, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 50-52)
      - Cross Electronics, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - United Fund- Bobby- Cerebral Palsy- Trinity Cathedral, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 2-4)
      - Mutual Benefit Life, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 5-6)
      - Personal- Tom at State YMCA- Swim Meet, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - United Fund- Louise Child Care & Vocational Rehabilitation Girl, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - United Fund- Vocational Rehabilitation Girl & Salvation Army Counselor, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - United Fund- Blind and Stroke Patients, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - United Fund- Stroke Patient and Family, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - United Fund- Cystic Fibrosis, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 13-16, 41-46, 49, 52)
      - Chatham College, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 17-25, 27-28, 39)
      - Community Services of Pennsylvania, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 26, 29-37)
      - Health & Welfare Association, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 38)
      - United Fund- McKees Rocks Boys Club, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 40)
      - United Fund, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 47-48, 50)
      - United Fund- Speech & Hearing, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 51)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 1-9)
      - United Fund, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 10-12)
      - Captain Cod's Restaurant, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Chris Martin's Wedding- New Jersey, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - United Fund- Hard Hat, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - United Fund- Vocational Rehabilitation Center Tour, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 16-17)
      - Beckman, Yoder and Seay, Inc., 1973 (Box 35, Folder 18-19)
      - Personal- Mellon Square/Walt Harper, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - United Fund Meeting- 1973 Campaign (Box 35, Folder 21-25)
      - Chatham College, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 26-28, 30, 44)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- Zoo, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 31-32, 34)
      - United Fund- Meeting, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 33)
      - United Fund- Volunteer Meeting (Box 35, Folder 35-36)
      - United Fund- Squirrel Hill Volunteers, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 38)
      - United Fund- Rotary Volunteers, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 39)
      - United Fund- Meeting- Mr. Ramsdell, Chairman (Box 35, Folder 42)
      - United Fund- West Mifflin- Steel Valley Volunteers, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 43)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 46-50)
      - United Fund- Lemmington Home for the Aged- Crafts Group, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 51-52)
      - United Fund- Lemmington Home for the Aged- Crafts Group, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - United Fund- Hill City Medical Center, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - United Fund- District Children & Foster Parents, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 3-5)
      - United Fund, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
      - Personal- III, Summarit, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 8, 13)
      - Personal- Church Clouds, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 10-12, 14-21)
      - Personal- Control test, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - Kellogg Media Group- H.J. Heinz, T. O'Reilly - Football game w/KMG, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - Kellogg Media Group- International Truck- W. B., 1973 (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - Kellogg Media Group- H.J. Heinz, Tom O'Reilly, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - GTI- (Jack Milligan), 1973 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - 1974
      Subjects included are Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children; Aetna Insurance; Shadyside Academy; Pittsburgh United Way; Mellon Bank; United Fund; Point Park; a male sportswear model; American Greetings submissions; and horses. Also included are Martin's personal photographs.
      - Fernway Civic Association- Congressman Clarke visit, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - Color File Copies- Sent to Greetings Corp., 1974 (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - Kit- Modeling, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - United Fund, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 30-31)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 32-36, 47-52)
      - Personal- IIIa Summarit, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 37)
      - United Fund- Volunteers- Ballet Tickets, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 38)
      - Health Research & Services Foundation Awards, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 39)
      - Personal, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 40, 44)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children Bowling, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 41-43)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- 20 Mile Walk, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 45)
      - Personal- Pittsburgh Diver, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 46)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 1, 35-37)
      - Bill Pflaum, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 2-4)
      - United Way- Wesley Center Eye Test, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 5, 7)
      - Personal- Leica III, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Health & Welfare Association- Governor Shapp, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Personal- 28 mm Test, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children- at the Meadows, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 10-11, 14-16)
      - Shady Side Academy, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 12-13, 17-32)
      - Chatham College- Dr. Eddy & Dr. Chan, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 33)
      - Met. Life- Medical Center Building Pittsburgh, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 34)
      - Aetna Insurance Company- Tri-State Fabricating Warrendale, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 38)
      - United Way- Lemmington Home for the Aged, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 39-40, 49)
      - United Way- St. Margaret's– Arthritis Patient, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 41-42)
      - July 4th Bradford Woods Festivities, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 43)
      - Mellon Bank, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 44)
      - Bradford Woods Aux. Fire Police, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 45)
      - Personal- Windwood Swim Pix, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 46)
      - Personal, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 47)
      - Volunteer Information Services, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 48, 51)
      - United Way, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 49)
      - Gail Weingarten- & "B.C.", 1974 (Box 37, Folder 50)
      - Personal- Copy of Letter to YOVA, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 52)
      - United Way- Vocational Rehabilitation Center Tour, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
      - United Way- Volunteer Chairman Meeting, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 3-4)
      - United Way- National Headquarters -Area Chairmen, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - United Way- Madame Summers (?), 1974 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - United Way- Cindy Ritchey, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - United Way- Barb Burns, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - United Way- Attorney F. Goldman & Hill House Meeting, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - United Way- Scouts & Boys Clubs, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 10-11)